Guide to the Edward E. Smuts Papers, 1945-1981 AIS.2012.07
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Urban Development Consultants, Inc., 1959-1981; VII.
  - Reports, Studies, and Proposals, 1960-1981; 7.
    - "A Plan and Program for Residential Development in Pittsburgh", 1965 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - "New Housing Site for Pittsburgh - Sweetbriar Hallock", August 1965 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - "Community Renewal Program Study", 1965 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - "New Housing Sites for Pittsburgh Greenway", August 1965 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - "Steep-Slop Housing - A Fesibility Report", August 1965 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - "Land Utilization and Marketability Study - Wilmerding Project NO. 1 PA.R-134", March 1966 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - "Market Impact Study of Selected Housing Developments in the Pittsburgh Area", 1967 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - "Land Utilization and Marketability Study - Ninth Street PA. R-210", March 1965 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - "Greater Pitt - Gateway to the World: A Study of the Feasibility of Establishing Greater Pitt As a Major International Airport", May 1969 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - "Soil and Foundation Report Northside Riverfront Improvement", 1969 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - "Strategies to Provide a Community Center St. Nicholas Cathedral", November 1970 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - "Fifth-Forbes Corridor Study", 1969 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - "An Action Program for Downtown Pittsburgh", 1970 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - "Carnegie Mellon University Spear - Klee Property Disposition Development", 1970 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - "Proposal for Pittsburgh Convention Exposition Center - Advisory Committee on Exhibition Hall", January 1970 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - "The Redevelopment Area Plan - Clifton Park Redevelopment Area No. 36", January 1970 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - "Action Housing, Inc. Semi-Annual Report to the Board of Directors", September 1971 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - "Action Housing, Inc. Chairman's Report 14th Annual Meeting", January 1972 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - "Action Housing, Inc. Chairman's Report 15th Annual Meeting", January 1973 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - "St. John's General Hospital Development Program", June 1973 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - "Sample Scheduling Documents", 1973 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - "A Community Profile of Lower Oakand", August 1974 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - "A Community Profile of North Oakand", August 1974 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - "A Community Profile of South Oakand", Auguest 1974 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - "Allegheny General Hospital, Divine Providence Hospital, St. John's Hospital - Ambulatory Care Planning for the Northside of Pittsburgh", January 1974 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - "Development Program for Health Care - A Summary", 1973-1981 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - "St. John's General Hospital - Plan/Program for Development", July 1976 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - "Housing and Community Development Amendments", 1978 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - "The Oakland Plan, A Citizens' Planning Process", 1977-1979 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - "Journal of the American Planning Association Volume 45, Number 2", April 1979 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - "Geo-Science Department Proposal for Subsurface Investigation", unknown (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - "City of Pittsburgh Residential, Commercial, and Industrial Real Estate for Sale", unknown (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - "West Hills Center Associates", unknown (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - "Port of Pittsburgh - Fact Finder", unknown (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - "Pittsburgh Profile", uknown (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - "Part II of Lease of Land for Private Redevelopment By and Between Urban Redevelopment Aurthority of Pittsburgh and St. Margaret Memorial Hospital", unknown (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - "For Sale: Downtown Pittsburgh", unknown (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - "St. John's Hospital Development Program Phase I", unknown (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Topical Folders, 1952-1981; 8.
    The subseries consists of project and subject files, generally these were not part of larger projects undertaken by the firm, but reflect a wide range of business activity and professional projects. Included are significant documentation on projects for Carnegie Mellon University, Craig Square Shops, Health Systems Consultants, Mine Safety Appliances, Point Park College, and Westinghouse. Content of the folders include: business correspondence, memorandums, handwritten notes, proposals, reference materials, statistics of the project area, financial reports, pamphlets, blueprints, press releases, maps, photographs, area data, and related published materials.
    - Abram, Leon, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Acquaah-Harrison Senathirajah Associates, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Action Housing - Rehabilitation Program, 1966-1967 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Administrative – Accounting File, 1971-1974 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Administrative – Armstrong County Contract, 1973-1979 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Administration – Work Program with Department of City Planning and Development, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Aiken Ave. Project, 1974-1980 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Allegheny – Property Tax Rates, 1962-1970 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Allegheny County Health Department - Advisory Council on Environmental Quality, 1970-1976 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Allegheny County Health Department - Pamphlets, 1968-1971 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Allegheny County - River Front Acquisition Project, 1971-1978 (Box 16, Folder 3-4)
    - Allegheny General Hospital - Consulting, 1973-1974 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Allis - Chalmers Manufacturing Company, 1952-1962 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Alman, Contract, 1975-1978 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - American Planning Association (APA) - Meeting Presentation Vacant/Sensitive Land Managment Study, unknown (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - American Society for Public Administration (ASAP) Pittsburgh Area Chapter and Conference, 1976-1983 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - ARA Project Follow-up, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Armstrong County - Coal Conversion, 1975-1976 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Arts and Crafts Center for Pittsburgh (ACCP) - Project Binder, 1968-1970 (Box 16, Folder 12-14)
    - Beynon, William, 1973-1980 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Billing - City of Sharon, 1971-1975 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Billing - St. John's General Hospital, 1970-1975 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Billing - Subcontractor Urban Design Associates (UDA), 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Board of Pubic Education - Pittsburgh, 1961-1970 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Branigar Organization, Inc., 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Bus-way 35 mm Slides, February 1976 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Carnegie Mellon University (CMU) General, 1974-1975 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - CMU - Blueprints, 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - CMU - Bureau of Mines, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - CMU- Courses Taught - City Planning and Urban Design, 1964-1967 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - CMU - Facilities Conditions and Deasign Criteria, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - CMU – Final Agreement Draft Executed, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - CMU – Forbes Craig Area Development, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - CMU – Lecture Series, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - CMU - Playhouse Real, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - CMU – Press Releases, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - CMU – Proposal, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - CMU – Project, 1971-1975 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - CMU – Spear-Klee Project, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Central Business District (Center 1) Market Square, 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Center Medical Pavilion, Inc., 1972-1977 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Center City Transportation Project – Downtown, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - City Planning Commission (CPC) Consulting Activity Reports, 1961-1964 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - CPC – Hearing, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - CPC – Industrial Contractual Details, 1960-1965 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Chateau-West Project, 1960-1961 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Clients – Action-Housing Inc., 1965 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Clients – Baskin, Sachs & Craig, 1964-1965 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Clients – Carnegie Institute of Technology, 1964-1965 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Clients – David, Lewis, and Associates, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Clients – Mine Safety Appliances Co., 1965 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Clients – Zanesville, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Columbia Corporation Follow-up, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Comprehensive Health Planning Association of Western Pennsylvania – Joint Planning Advisory Committee, March 1976 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Consad Research Corporation – Industrial, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Constantin Property, 1972-1974 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Continental Colonies, Inc. – Residential Land Development, 1971-1975 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Continental Colonies, Inc. – Maps, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Continental Insurance Companies, 1970-1973 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence, 1972-1977 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Counseling Center of Pittsburgh – Alan Dezen, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Craig Street Development, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Craig Square Shops – Agey, Jim, & Robert Young – Decorators, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Craig Square Shops – Baty, Richland – Leather and Antiques, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Craig Square Shops – D.Lyon – Fur's Shop, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Craig Square Shops – Elias, David – Coffee Express, Inc., 1981 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Craig Square Shops – Hackeny – Flowers, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Craig Square Shops – Individual Prospects, 1977-1980 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Craig Square Shops – Kedzuf – Haircut Services, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Craig Square Shops – Kenny, Fran – Ice Cream Parlor, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Craig Square Shops – Parent, Evelyn – Panhandler, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Craig Square Shops - Retail Leasing, 1977-1980 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Craig Square Shops – Schmid, Joan – Gilded Cage, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Craig Square Shops – Small, Norma – Leather, unknown (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Craig Square Shops Prospect - Ciccone, Dennis, and Gerald Farbar - Bookstore, 1979-1981 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Craig Square Shops Prospect – Whetstone, Roy – Whetstone Environments, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - CRP – Residential – Conjoining Housing Analysis, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - CRP – Residential – Housing Act, 1965-1966 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - CRP – Residential – Housing Development Study AREA, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - CRP – Residential – Housing Market Study, 1964-1965 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - CRP – Residential – Occupancy – Vacancy Data, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - CRP – Residential – Population Estimates, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Department of Transportation (US), 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Department of Water - Gallery Area, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Dithridge-Bellefield Project, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Downtown Action Program, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Duclos, Paul J., 1970 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Duquesne Light, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Duquesne Light-Brunot Island Project, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Duquesne Light Company – Area Development Manual 1, 1961-1964 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Duquesne Stag Products Co., 1965 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - East Suburban Health Center/Forbes Health Systems: Maps and Design Plans, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - East Liberty/Lincon Ave. Area: Photographs and Negatives, unknown (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - EDP, 1964-1970 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Environmental Design Advisor Committee – Reference Materials, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Environmental Design Advisory Committee – Program, 1960-1969 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Estate Data – Administrative, 1969-1975 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Feasibility Study Bikeway System Allegheny County, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Federal Arts Program, 1980-1981 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Fees and Contract Pricing Information, unknown (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Forbes Health System, 1976-1977 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Forbes Hosptal System-Site Analysis Project, 1976-1977 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Forbes-Oakland Medical Building, 1975-1977 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Franken, Dr. Paul - Syndikud Der Dresdner Bank Germany, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Gay Cruising Area- South Craig Street, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Graphics Plus, 1970-1978 (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Green Engineering, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Grodin, Marsha - Sachs Realty Forbes and Craig, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Hammer, Siler, George Associate, Inc., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Hartford Process - American City Corporation, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Healthy Center Contract University of Pittsburgh, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Health Care Planning, 1977-1978 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Health System Consultants (HSC) General, 1974-1978 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - HSC-Alcoa Assignments, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - HSC- Experience and Services Orientation of UDC, unknown (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - HSC - Garland, Gray, 1970-1978 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - HSC - Marketing Program, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - HSC - Stark Nathan J., 1975-1979 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Homes, Ryan, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Hotel Chain Information, 1970-1972 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Hotel Company - Aircoa, unknown (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Housing for the Elderly, 1967-1970 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Hospital Association of Pennsylvania – Impact of Government Regulations on Hospital Costs (A-D), 1977 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Hospital Association of Pennsylvania – Impact of Government Regulations on Hospital Costs (D-K), 1977 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Hospital Holding Companies, 1977-1978 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Hospital Investment Summary, 1973-1977 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Howard Christner and Carnegie Mellon University (HC/CMU) General, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - HC/CMU – Agreement Modifications, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - HC/CMU – Design and Zoning Analysis, 1971-1974 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - HC/CMU – Dithridge Parking, 1972-1974 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - HC/CMU – Parking Negotiation, 1971-1975 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - HC/CMU –Pittsburgh Blind Association, 1973-1975 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - HC/CMU – Project Follow-Up, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - HC/CMU – Real Estate, 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - HC/CMU – Underground Parking Project, 1973-1975 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - HC/CMU – Zoning Petition Endorsement Letters, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - HC/CMU – Zoning Petition Information, 1972-1975 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Joseph A. Hajnas and Associates (Landscape Architects), 1971 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Joseph Horne Company, 1960-1964 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Kanter Corporation, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Leasing Reference, 1973-1979 (Box 20, Folder 1-2)
    - Lesko, Ruth, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - LFDR Design Consultants, Inc., 1975 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - LaNormande Restaurant, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Leggett, William D. Company Site – Market Study, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Little, Arthur D. & Co., 1970 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Lipsitz, Herman, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Magee-Oxford, 1978-1979 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Martin, Albert C. & Associates – Resources (Architects/Planning), 1970-1972 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Mauro, John T., 1971 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Maryland Creek-Yorker Contracts, 1976-1977 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Maus, Vernes, 1962-1964 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - McGarrahan, John, 1971-1973 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - McMillan, Norman H., 1977 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - MDC Systems, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Medicon, Inc., 1974 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Mercy Hospital – Hospice Committee and Planning Group, 1978-1979 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Miller, Paul, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Mine Safety Appliances (MSA) General, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - MSA – Assessments, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - MSA – Bacharach Industrial Instrument Co., 1964 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - MSA – Contract, 1973-1976 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - MSA – Correspondence, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - MSA- Sable Project, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - MSA- Maps and Charts, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - MSA- Penn Hills, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - MSA- Scherger, Ralph, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - MSA- Skidmore, Owings, & Merrill, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Miscellaneous, 1971-1978 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Mon Plaza, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Morgan, Pan, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Mountain Real Estate, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Mullen, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - New Towns & Town Centers for Pittsburgh Region, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - National Association of Olmstead Parks, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - National Regional Trends – Industrial Modernization, 1959-1965 (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - Nicaragua, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - Noise Control Committee-Board, 1973-1976 (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - Norris, Barry N., 1971-1972 (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - Oakland – Alternate Future Consultants, 1975-1977 (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - Oakland – "B" Exhibit, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 42)
    - Oakland – Berardennelli Property, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 43)
    - Oakland – CMU Properties, 1976-1978 (Box 20, Folder 44)
    - Oakland – College Club, unknown (Box 20, Folder 45)
    - Oakland – Condominium Project, unknown (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Oakland – Crosskeys (Ramada), unknown (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Oakland – Design Consultant Section, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Oakland – East of Craig/Fifth & Neville Apartment Site, unknown (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Oakland – Pittsburgh Fairfax, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Oakland – Flinn Property, 1972-1974 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Oakland – Health Center Planning, 1974-1976 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Oakland – Historical Property Project, unknown (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Oakland – Historical – St. Paul's Cathedral, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Oakland – Hotel, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Oakland – JDJ Associates –Advertising and Public Relations, 1981-1982 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Oakland – Kriss-Nan Properties, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Oakland – Kriss-Nan 2 – Pitcher, 1968-1973 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Oakland – Kriss-Nan 3 –Joel Kranich Offer, 1972-1974 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Oakland – Magee Follow-Up, 1973-1976 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Oakland – Magee-McNeil Contract, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Oakland – Magee Project, 1973-1974 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Oakland – Magee Property 1, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Oakland – Magee Property 2, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Oakland – Magee Zoning Analysis, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Oakland – Oxford-Magee Parking Lease, 1978-1979 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Oakland – PAT/Magee Acquisitions Agreement, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Oakland – PAT/Magee Project, 1973-1974 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Oakland – Pittsburgh Plan for Art (Baloh), 1972-1975 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Oakland – Playhouse, 1971-1976 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Oakland – Smith, Thelma-319 S Craig Street, 1972-1976 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Oakland – South Craig Area – Liquor Store (LCB and Private), unknown (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Oakland – Transit, 1970-1978 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Oakland – Transportation Study (Preliminary Draft), 1979 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Oakland – Western PA. Association for the Blind, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Oakland – West University Place, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Oliver Realty, Inc., 1970-1979 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Oxford Development, 1971-1974 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - PAT-Rapid Transit Early Action Program, 1967-1970 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Page & Company, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Palmer, Thomas, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Pennsylvania Planning Association, (PPA) –Conference, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Pennsylvania Railroad Negotiations Chartiers Valley Project, 1958-1964 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Penn Central Area –Development Project Convention Center, 1971-1972 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Penn Central Photographs, unknown (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Penn's Southwest Association, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Penn's Southwest – Ad Campaign, 1980-1981 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Pittsburgh-Allegheny County Cultural Alliance –"The Arts Edge" Conference, October 1981 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Pittsburgh Center for the Arts, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Pittsburgh City Planning Department – Citizen Participation Conference, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Pittsburgh Field Club, 1966-1977 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Pittsburgh Housing Land Bank Fund, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Pittsburgh Public Theater, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Pittsburgh Regional Planning Association, 1964-1975 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Pine Township, unknown (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Phipps Plaza, Atlanta, Ga., 1971 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Plateau Demont, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Point Park Playhouse, 1973-1979 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Point Park Playhouse – Contract, 1976-1979 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Point Park Playhouse – Current Follow-up Playhouse, 1975-1978 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Point Park Playhouse - Maps and Blueprints, unknown (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Point Park Playhouse – New Construction Option, unknown (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Point Park Playhouse Project, 1974-1976 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Point Park Playhouse Property - Magee Hospital/Point Park College, 1974-1978 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Point Park Playhouse – PHEFA, 1974-1976 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Point Park Playhouse – Street Vacation, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Point Park –Dormitory Properties, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Point Park – Dormitory Properties – Expenses & Billing, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Port Authority – Early Action Program Agreements, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Port Authority – Reference, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Port Authority of Allegheny County – Transit Concept Materials, 1966-1968 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Port Authority of Allegheny County – Transit, 1968-1969 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Port Authority – UDC Proposal-Contract-Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Post Office, 1963-1969 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Professional Director, unknown (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Programming System for Office of the Secretary of Defense, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Prudential – Follow-Up, 1959-1960 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Public Parking Programs, 1958-1967 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Real Estate –Federal Investors, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Rapid Transit – Shopping Center Development, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Real Estate Investor –Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Real Estate – Toten Property, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Real Estate Investors – National, 1962-1965 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Real Estate – Housing 236 Financing Programs, 1970-1971 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - REACON Corporation, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Receipts from Commissions, 1974-1976 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Regional Medical Program, 1972-1974 (Box 23, Folder 16-17)
    - Regional Planning Association, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Regional Economic Study Project, 1960-1985 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Renaissance II – Symposium, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Resources Investment, Inc., 1979 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Rice Center Project – Value Capture, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Richner, Ernest – Santo Domingo, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Rourke, Anthony –SMMH, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Rouse –Columbia Residential Deal, unknown (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Rowell, Harry B. Jr., 1974 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Rudov, Elaine, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Rust Engineering Company, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Sable, 1970-1977 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Sable, James R. – Billing and Contract, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Sable - Maps, unknown (Box 23, Folder 31)